New female teacher seducing
유혹하는 신임 여교사
Production and distribution of subtitles KUKUDAS.COM
자막 제작, 배포 쿠쿠다스닷컴 KUKUDAS.COM
Strategy (reduced) brother
전략(줄임) 오빠
Are you used to living in the upper countryside?
윗쪽 지방 생활에는 익숙해졌어?
Isn't it just eating out?
외식만 하고 있는거 아니야?
Washing must be done twice a week.
세탁도 일주일에 두번정도는 꼭 해야돼
Take a bath
목욕도 꼭 하고
I also want to be a teacher
나도 염원하던 교사가 되고
3 months have passed
3개월이 지났어
I'm still a novice teacher Every day is continuous learning
아직 초짜 교사라서 매일이 배움에 연속이야
Boys high school
남자 고등학교라
Sometimes I feel a bit ugly
조금 야한 시선을 느낄때도 있지만
Everyone is honest and cute.
다들 솔직하고 귀여운 애들이야
It's really different from your brother.
오빠랑은 정말 다르네
Hello sir - Hi
선생님 안녕하세요 - 안녕
What..
뭐..
It may be similar to that
야하다는 점은 비슷할지도 모르지만
Anyway, I chose this teacher job
어찌됐든 이 교사라는 직업을 선택한 이상
Face to face with students
전력으로 학생들과 마주하여
To help them grow I'll work hard
그들이 성장해 나가는데 도움이 되도록 열심히 할게
Even my brother Don't worry about mom and dad
오빠도 엄마랑 아빠한테 걱정 좀 끼치지말고
I'll write a letter again
또 편지 쓸게
-Chinami
- 치나미
(Classes pass)
(수업내용은 패스)
Now what I read
자 지금 읽은걸
I'll write it on the blackboard
칠판에 적을테니까
For everyone to write
다들 필기하도록
xx group (It's a name, but I can't hear it because of the background music)
xx군 (이름인데 배경음악때문에 안들려요)
Yeah ... Uh ... how many pages?
응... 어... 몇페이지였지?
Did you hear correctly? - Sorry
제대로 들었어? - 죄송합니다
Page 27
27페이지
Really ~ Listen carefully when the teacher speaks - Sorry
정말~ 선생님이 말할때 잘 들어야지 - 죄송합니다
I'm going to take the next class
지금 수업하는 부분은 다음 시험에 나와
Ah yes
아.. 네
I have to review it when I go home.
집에 돌아가서도 복습해야돼
Okay
알겠습니다
I couldn't keep focusing on the class
계속 수업에 집중 못하던데
What were you thinking?
무슨 생각하고 있던거야?
Ah ... something like the entertainment program I saw yesterday ...
아.. 어제 본 예능 프로그램 같은거요..
Entertainment? What did you see?
예능? 뭐 봤었는데?
28 hours you shouldn't laugh (* Kakinotsukai's Never Laughing Series) (About 6 hours on special broadcast on December 31 of the year)
웃으면 안되는 28시간 (*가키노츠카이의 절대로 웃으면 안되는 시리즈) (연말 12월 31일에 스페셜방송으로 6시간정도)
Have you seen it all the time?
계속 그거 봤었어?
Yeah -That's why you lack sleep.
네 - 그래서 수면부족이구나
The teacher likes the pro,
선생님도 그 프로 좋아하지만
So, you look like a little comedian?
그러고보니 너 조금 개그맨 같은데?
is that so?
그런가요?
that's right
맞아 맞아
character
자
Stop chatting
잡담은 그만하고
I'll take it again - Yeah
다시 수업할게요 - 네
Can I sit? - Huh
앉아도 돼요? - 응
(Classes pass)
(수업내용은 패스)
Production and distribution of subtitles KUKUDAS.COM
자막 제작, 배포 쿠쿠다스닷컴 KUKUDAS.COM
Suzuki-kun
스즈키군
Why is it that you don't want to come to school?
학교에 오기 싫다는거 왜 그런거야?
Why is that ...
왜 그런건지..
I don't know either
저도 잘 모르겠어요
I need to know the reason to solve it
이유를 알아야 해결을 하지
Perhaps? Are you being bullied?
혹시? 왕따 당하고 있는건 아니지?
No it's not like that
아니요 그런건 아닌데요
What
뭐랄까
That's it
그거에요
Class or
수업이나
Like a side activity
부활동 같은거
Like that
그런게
I want to know what it means
무슨 의미가 있나 싶어서
I'm not sure
그런걸 잘 모르겠어요
But ...
그런.. 그래도
School is a fun place
학교는 즐거운곳이야
For example
예를들면
Well..
음..
That ... for example
그.. 예를들면
Like a sports event
운동회라던가
And..
그리고..
Festival or something
축제라던가
Well..
음..
No, I'm not interested in that.
아니 그런거에 흥미 없어요
Are you done now?
이제 됐나요?
Wait a minute
잠깐만
What else is fun ...
즐거운게 또 뭐가 있나..
For example..
예를들면..
That..
그..
Well..
음..
And .. the athletic meet.
그리고.. 운동회는.. 아까 말했지?
The festival ...
축제도... 말했고
And ... ah!
그리고.. 아!
I have a school trip
수학여행도 있고
And...
그리고...
In spring
봄에
There are suburban learning
교외학습도 있고
And..
그리고..
It's fun to eat lunch together
다같이 점심 먹는것도 즐겁고
Um ... again ...
음.. 또.. 부활동이라던가
Well..
음..
And there are swimming lessons in summer
그리고 여름엔 수영수업도 있잖아
And..
그리고..
Well..
음..
In the fall?
가을엔?
It would be fun to grill and eat sweet potatoes together (?? actually said, not paraphrase)
다같이 군고구마 구워먹는것도 즐겁겠다 (?? 실제로 이렇게 말했습니다 의역아님)
And..
그리고..
Sweet potato is so delicious ~
군고구마 엄청~ 맛있지
Hard ~ Hot ~
딱딱하고~ 뜨겁고~
My teacher loves sweet potatoes too.
선생님도 군고구마 너무 좋아해
Especially hard is better
특히 딱딱한게 더 좋으려나
Suzuki-kun also likes sweet potatoes?
스즈키군도 군고구마 좋아해?
The teacher
선생님은
The sweet potato is hard ~ thick ~ I like hot
군고구마는 딱딱하고~ 굵고~ 뜨거운게 좋아
Haa ... for some reason ...
하아.. 왠지..
I want to eat sweet potatoes
군고구마가 먹고 싶어졌어
I know what Suzuki-kun is happy to do.
스즈키군이 즐거워 할만한게 뭔지 알겠다
on...? Teacher...?
에...? 선생님...?
no..
아니..
Do you like it?
좋아하지?
No ... there ... it's ...
아니... 저기.. 그건..
Huh? Don't you like
응? 안 좋아해?
Ah ... Joe. I like it.
아.. 조..좋아해요
Teacher
선생님이
School is a fun place
학교가 즐거운곳 이라는걸
I'll let you know
알려줄게
I ... really?
저..정말요?
Want to touch more?
좀 더 만지고 싶어?
Ah.
아..으..네.. 좀 더..
Teacher..? Really?
선생님..? 진짜에요?
(Not on clothes) Do you want to touch it yourself?
(옷위로 말고)직접 만지고 싶지?
character - It's okay?
자 - 괜찮아요?
Touch it
만져봐
Teacher's chest soft?
선생님 가슴 부드러워?
Yes ... it's very soft
네.. 엄청 부드러워요
Good mood? How is your teacher's chest?
기분 좋아? 선생님 가슴이 어때?
Ah
아.. 엄청 좋아요
The teacher feels good too
선생님도 기분 좋아
really?
정말요?
Okay?
알겠어?
The nipple is hard
젖꼭지 딱딱해졌어
Ah yes..
아.. 네..
Touch me a little more
좀 더 만져줘
Teacher ... Even if you do something like this ... Is it okay?
선생님.. 이런거 해도.. 괜찮은거에요..?
Suzuki-kun
스즈키군이
I want to have fun at school.
학교에 즐겁게 왔으면 좋겠어서 그래
Do you want to suck your chest?
가슴 빨고 싶지 않아?
Ah ... I want to suck
아..빨고 싶어요
then
그럼
Ah, good
아 좋아
Keep sucking
계속 빨아줘
Yeah..
네..
Did you enjoy school?
학교가 즐거워졌어?
Ah .. school ... it's fun
아.. 학교.. 즐거워요
School is a fun place
학교는 즐거운 곳이야
Teacher...
선생님...
Suzuki-kun's sweet potato is hard
스즈키군의 군고구마 딱딱해졌네
Ah!
아!
Can I see you?
선생님이 봐도 될까?
It's okay?
괜찮아요?
Wait a minute ... I'm getting hot ...
잠깐.. 제가 지금.. 달아올라서..
Show me Suzuki's hot sweet potato
스즈키꾼의 후끈한 군고구마 보여줘
Amazing
엄청나
Hard
딱딱하고
Coarse
굵고
Hot
뜨거워
more
좀 더
Make the sweet potato hard
군고구마 딱딱하게 해봐
Where are you weak?
어디가 약한거야?
If you wash it, it will be harder
빨아주면 좀 더 딱딱해질거에요
Can the teacher eat?
선생님이 먹어도 돼?
Yes please eat mine
네 제꺼 먹어어주세요
I will enjoy this food
잘 먹겠습니다
Good
좋아
Teacher..
선생님..
How about mine?
제꺼.. 어때요..?
Suzuki-kun's sweet potato is really delicious
스즈키군의 군고구마 엄청 맛있어
Sweet honey comes from the glans
귀두에서 달콤한 꿀이 나오네
Teacher..
선생님..
Please taste everything (do not wash the front)
제꺼(앞쪽만 빨지 말고) 전부 맛봐주세요
then
그럼
Deeply
깊숙히
Sir ... this is the best ...
선생님.. 이거.. 최고에요..
Suzuki-kun's too big to go in.
스즈키군꺼 너무 커서 전부 안들어가네
Did you enjoy school?
학교 즐거워 졌어?
Yes, it's fun
네.. 즐거워요
Then to be more enjoyable
그럼 더 즐거워 지기위해서
Suzuki-kun's sweet potato
스즈키군의 군고구마
Should I put it on my chest?
가슴에 끼워볼까?
It's okay?
괜찮아요?
Ah ..
아..엄청나..
It feels warm
따뜻한게 기분 좋아요
Ah ... my sweet potato is getting hot ..
아..제 군고구마가.. 뜨거워져요..
Make it hotter
좀 더 뜨겁게해봐
Do you like your heart?
선생님 가슴 좋아?
good
좋아요
If you can't stand it
참을수 없으면
You can wrap the white honey
하얀 꿀 싸도돼
really?
정말요?
Wrap it in your heart
선생님 가슴에 많이 싸줘
Then teacher ... keep going. I love this
그럼 선생님.. 그대로 계속 해주세요 이거 너무 좋아요
this?
이거?
I can't stand it ...
못 참겠어요..
I don't have to hold up
참지 않아도 돼
Wrap it in your heart
선생님 가슴에 싸줘
Ah, I think it will be cheap ..
아 선생님 쌀것 같아요..
Ah .. cheap .. -Wrap it up
아.. 싼다.. - 싸줘
Teacher on the chest
선생님 가슴에
A lot of white honey came out
하얀 꿀이 많이 나왔네
Should I clean it?
청소를 해야겠지?
on?
에?
then
그럼
Will you come to school tomorrow?
내일도 학교 와줄거지?
Ah yes..
아.. 네..
From now on, I will come out without missing
이제부터 빠지지 않고 나올게요
Production and distribution of subtitles KUKUDAS.COM
자막 제작, 배포 쿠쿠다스닷컴 KUKUDAS.COM
(Classes pass) (Keep talking about utopia)
(수업내용은 패스) (계속 유토피아 얘기만 나오네요)
OK?
괜찮아?
Are you listening?
잘 듣고있어?
Yeah
네
Then I will continue reading
그럼 계속 읽을게
Moreover, the will of this control
거기다 이러한 통제의 의지는
It also affects human physiological reasoning.
인간의 생리적인 이치에도 영향을 미친다
Therefore, utopia
그러므로 유토피아는
The human five senses are orderly and reasonably Couldn't it have been controlled?
인간의 오감을 질서있게 합리적으로 통제를 할수 있었던것 아닐까?
And I Human five senses
그리고 필자는 인간의 오감중
When it comes to sight, hearing, taste, and touch
시각, 청각, 미각, 촉각에 관해서는
Isn't it possible to control artificially? And think
인공적으로 제어하는것이 가능한게 아닐까 하고 생각해본다
Then would you like to solve the next question?
그럼 다음문제 풀어볼래?
Tell me when you're done
다 풀면 얘기해줘
Are you done?
다 풀었어?
No ... not yet ...
아뇨.. 아직..
Whoa ... really ~
후.. 정말~
I couldn't concentrate on the class, so I asked him to let me know again That's Nakano-kun.
수업에 집중을 못해서 다시 알려달라고한거 나카노군 이잖아
Now try hard
자 열심히 해봐
Yes .. sorry
네.. 죄송합니다
I can't concentrate at all
역시 전혀 집중을 못하네
Ah .. it's not .. it's not that ...
아.. 아니에요..그게 아니고..
Nakano-kun
나카노군은
I need training to develop concentration.
집중력을 키우는 트레이닝이 필요하겠어
on?
에?
During class, I only focus on the class.
수업중엔 수업에만 집중하는거야
Yeah..
네..
Now is
지금은
Focus on teacher panties
선생님 팬티에 집중해
Yeah
네
Look from a different angle this time
이번엔 다른 각도에서 봐봐
What do you think?
어때?
I can see well from below
밑에서 잘 보여요
Come closer and look
좀 더 가까이 와서 봐
Concentrate
집중해
see?
보여?
Teacher wears tea bag panties
선생님 티백팬티 입었어
Do you like these panties?
이런 팬티 좋아해?
yes I like it
네.. 좋아해요
Look closer
더 자세히 봐
Would you like to make it look better?
더 잘보이게 해줄까?
Do you see better?
더 잘보이지?
Yeah
네
Look
봐줘
see?
보여?
Yeah..
네..
It looks really good
엄청 잘 보여요
Isn't it more focused than panties?
팬티보다 더 집중 잘되지?
Yes ..
네.. 엄청..
Focus
집중되요
I can see everything inside
안쪽까지 다 보여요
What's going on inside the teacher?
선생님의 안쪽 어떻게 되있어?
very..
엄청..
It's twinkling (wet)
반짝반짝 거려요(젖어서)
Maybe so
그럴지도 모르겠네
Nakano-kun looked at me like that
나카노군이 그렇게 쳐다보니까
The teacher was sparkling
선생님이 반짝거리게 되었어
Would you like to make it look better?
더 잘보이게 해줄까?
See you more
더 봐줘
I'll show you this ass
이번엔 엉덩이 보여줄게
Yeah
네
That's amazing
엄청나네
see?
보여?
Yeah
네
It looks really good
엄청 잘 보여요
Do you see the teacher's ass?
선생님 똥꼬도 보여?
Butts are also pretty
똥꼬도 엄청 이뻐요
Focus
집중해서 봐
Nakanokun - Yeah
나카노쿤 - 네
I'm very focused
엄청 집중하고 있어요
Look at this
이쪽도 봐줘
then
그럼
Another place this time
이번엔 다른곳
Look closer
더 가까이서 봐
Yeah
네
How's your nipple?
선생님 젖꼭지 어때?
It got bigger
커졌어요
Stick out your tongue - Yeah
혀 내밀어봐 - 네
Gently suck
부드럽게 빨아줘
It's the best
최고에요
Even bite - Yeah
물기도 해봐 - 네
The left hand is this
왼손은 이쪽
Turn your tongue more
더 혀를 돌려봐
Yeah
네
Ah, good
아 좋아
Are you focused now? - Yeah
이제 집중되지? - 네
Close your eyes and feel a lot
눈감고 많이 느껴봐
Focus your nerve here
여기에 신경을 집중시켜
Is it there?
거기에요?
Focus more
더 집중해
Are you focusing?
집중하고 있지?
Yeah
네
then
그럼
I'll focus on big cocks
큰자지에 집중시켜줄게
Focus on the glans
귀두에 집중해
Appreciate because the teacher will give you a blowjob
선생님이 입으로 해줄테니까 감상
Please explain
잘 설명해줘
Yeah
네
Teacher mouth
선생님 입속
Very warm
엄청 따뜻하고
My heart is shaking
가슴이 흔들리고
In the mouth
입속에서
Erotic flows a lot
에로가 엄청 흘러나와서
So good
너무 좋아요
good job
참 잘 했어요
Teacher with tongue
선생님 혀로
What are you getting now?
지금 뭘 받고 잇는거야?
With the front of the cock
자지 앞쪽과
Back side
뒷쪽을
I'm sucking my feet
족쪽 빨아주고 있어요
Want to increase your concentration on your cock?
자지에 집중력을 더 늘리고 싶어?
Yeah
네
Focus on your cock
자지에 집중해
Then put it in?
그럼 넣는다?
Yeah
네
How's your teacher pussy now?
선생님 보지 지금 어떻게 됐어?
It's very slippery
엄청 미끌미끌해요
Slippery
미끌미끌해서
The cock ...
자지가..
Go deep
깊숙히 들어가요
Focus more
더 집중해봐
more
더
Move more
더 움직여줘
Yeah
네
Should we try changing directions?
방향 바꿔서 해볼까?
more
좀 더
Drive it to the teacher more
좀 더 선생님한테 박아줘
I can't sleep
몸을 못 가누겠어
Ah ..
아..간다..
So good
너무 좋아요
Nakano-gun - Yeah
나카노군 - 네
come here
이쪽으로 와
this time
이번엔
Come this way - Yeah
이쪽으로 - 네
I'll put it
넣을게요
Focus your nerves on your cock
자지에 신경을 집중시켜
Yeah
네
Thicker than before
아까보다 더 두꺼워졌어
Did your sense of cock change? - Yeah
자지의 감각이 바꼇지? - 네
More than before
아까보다 더
Tighten more
더 조여와요
Oh good
아 좋다
I think cocks get eaten
자지가 잡아 먹히는것 같아요
Nakano Islands
나카노군도
You can move
움직여도 돼
Yeah
네
Then I'll move now
그럼 지금 움직여 볼게요
Move it
움직여봐
Can you hear the creaking?
찔꺽찔꺽 거리는거 들려?
I can hear you
들려요
Teacher pussy
선생님 보지를
Make it squeak more
더 질꺽찔꺽 거리게 해줘
Yeah
네
I think I will go again
선생님 또 갈것 같아
Goes..
간다..
Ah, good..
아..좋아..
Oh no ... go again ...
아 안돼.. 또 가버려..
Teacher..
선생님..
Teacher
선생님
Focus on your cock and lips
자지에도 입술에도 집중해
Yeah
네
Ah
아~ 좋아
Good
좋아
Do you feel the teacher's pussy tight?
선생님 보지 꽉 조이는거 느껴지지?
Yeah
네
I think I will go
갈것 같아
Go again ...
또 가버려..
Ah ..
아..간다..
Teacher
선생님
I think my concentration will be lost
저 집중력이 끈어질것 같아요
Are you already losing attention?
벌써 집중력이 끈어지는거야?
Yes .. It's the limit of concentration ...
네.. 집중력의 한계에요..
Good
좋아
The teacher will take it by mouth
선생님이 입으로 받아줄게
Teacher in mouth
선생님 입에
I'll cook -Wrap it up
쌀게요 - 싸줘
Ah, teacher ...
아..선생님..
(Cheap)
(싸도)좋아
Ah, teacher.
아..선생님..싸요..
Teacher ..
선생님..가요..
Good
좋아
Go
가줘
Ah ...
아 간다..
There are so many
이렇게 많이 나왔네
What do you think?
어때?
Do you think your concentration has increased?
집중력이 좀 높아진거 같아?
Yeah
네
From now on, you can't concentrate on classes ~
이제부터 수업에 집중못하면 안돼~
Production and distribution of subtitles KUKUDAS.COM
자막 제작, 배포 쿠쿠다스닷컴 KUKUDAS.COM
Ah here
아 여기다
Imada
이마다군
Give me the next one - Ah yes
다음거 줘 - 아 네
Alright
좋아쓰
Thanks for helping both
둘다 도와줘서 고마워
Well, we are the book committee
뭐 저희들 일단은 도서위원이니까
You read a book even after school.
선생님 방과후에도 책 읽으시는군요
it is a secret
비밀이야
I was ashamed to see something in the school office
교무실에서 보면 뭔가 부끄러워서
I'm studying in the classroom after school.
방과후에 교실에서 공부하고 있어
i See
그렇군요
Then give me that next time - Yeah
그럼 다음에는 그거줘봐 - 네
Where was it?
어디였지?
There ...
저 부근에..
Not here
여기도 아니고
Here it is
역시 여기야
You two - Yeah
너희 둘 - 네
now
지금
To hold the teacher's chair safely Isn't it without responsibility?
선생님의 의자를 안전하게 잡고 있는다는 책임감이 없는거 아니야?
Yeah? Did you hold well?
네? 잘 잡고있었지?
Huh
응
really?
정말로?
Really?
정말?
Really foot
정말 발쪽을
Was it looking right?
제대로 보고 있던걸까?
Did you keep looking at your feet?
계속 선생님의 발을 본걸까?
You were watching panties too?
역시 팬티 보고 있었지?
For you two
너희 둘에게는
I need to properly teach that responsibility
책임감이란걸 제대로 가르쳐야 겠어
Responsibility?
책임감이요?
Yes responsibility
그래 책임감
First you
먼저 너부터
I'll explain the responsibility
책임감에 대하여 설명해줄게
Ah yes..
아 네..
When a woman approaches this way
여성이 이런식으로 접근하면
Men have an erection
남성은 발기할 의무가 있어
An erection duty?
발기할 의무요?
okay
그래
Women are approaching like this first
여성이 먼저 이렇게 접근하는거야
It's irresponsible for a man who doesn't have an erection.
발기하지 않는 남자따위는 무책임한거야
Okay?
알겠어?
Yeah
네
Why are your hands playing
왜 손이 놀고 있어
Teacher ... what should I do?
선생님.. 어떻게 해야하죠?
If the woman did this much
여성이 이정도까지 해줬으면
Of course I have to touch it
당연히 만져줘야지
You have a duty to touch
너한테는 만질 의무가 있다고
Yeah
네
For men, touch the chest (not on clothes) directly Is there an obligation?
남자에겐 가슴을 (옷 위에서 말고)직접 만질 의무도 있겠죠?
I understand quickly
이해가 빠르네
character
자
Men also have a duty to take off
남성에겐 벗길 의무도 있어
Wow ~ that ’s great
와~ 대단해요
What is 'Teacher's heart is pretty'?
'선생님 가슴 이뻐요' 는?
Teacher's chest is pretty
선생님 가슴 이뻐요
Wow ~
와~
Are you satisfied with the bra?
브라자 위로 만족하는거야?
No ... I want to touch it myself
아니.. 직접 만지고 싶어요
So you're obliged to take your bra off, too?
그럼 브라자도 벗길 의무가 있는 거겠지?
Ah yes
아..네
Teacher's chest is so pretty
선생님 가슴 엄청 이뻐요
Teacher so pretty
선생님 너무 이뻐요
That's amazing
엄청나네
The man is also obliged to bury his face in his chest. I think there is
남자한테는 얼굴을 가슴에 파묻을 의무도 있다고 생각하는데요
right
그렇지
You have to do it
하지않으면 안되는거지
Ah, teacher ...
아..선생님..
Wow ~
와~ 쩔어
There is also a duty to suck the nipple I think
젖꼭지 빨아야하는 의무도 있다고 생각하는데요
right
맞아
Suck - Yeah
빨아 - 네
Female breast sucking
여성의 가슴 빨고
I have a duty to suck my cock
자지를 빨딱 세울 의무가 있어
Stand up a little more - Yeah
좀 더 세워봐 - 네
I can't say I've done my job this way.
이정도로는 책임을 다했다고 볼 수 없어
I will be careful
네 조심할게요
I have a duty to pick up more cocks
좀 더 자지를 빨딱 세울 의무가 있다고
You have to wrap a very thick semen - Yeah
엄청 진한 정액을 싸줘야돼 - 네
Ah ... sir ..
아.. 선생님..
I think it will be cold - Why?
쌀것 같아요.. - 왜?
I have to wrap it all out
전부 싸야돼 전부 뽑아내
A lot
많이 나왔네
Because it was wrapped so much
이렇게 많이 싸줬으니까
Does the teacher have a duty to clean it?
선생님도 깨끗하게 해줄 의무가 있겠지?
What do you think?
어때?
Do you know what responsibility is?
책임감이 무엇인지 알겠어?
Yeah
네
I have to be a responsible man
책임감이 있는 남자가 되어야해
Ugh ... teacher ...
윽...선생님..
Where is the erogenous zone?
어디가 성감대 일까?
The nipple is ... so good ...
젖꼭지는...너무 좋아요..
Do you like nipples? - Yeah
젖꼭지가 좋아? - 네
Because the teacher is serving the nipples like this
선생님이 이렇게 젖꼭지에 봉사해주고 있으니까
You're obligated to suck your cock.
자지를 빨딱 세울 의무가 있는거야
Yeah..
네..
Now, how do I make my nipples red?
자 젖꼭지를 어떻게 하면 빨딱 설까?
Roll your fingers ..
손가락으로.. 굴려주세요..
Do you want to roll it? - Yeah
굴려줬으면 좋겠어? - 네
like this?
이렇게?
I feel good
기분 좋아요
Nipples are starting to erect.
젖꼭지도 발기되기 시작했네
Nipple with responsibility ~
책임감이 있는 젖꼭지네~
Do you want to suck your nipples?
젖꼭지 빨아줬으면 좋겠어?
Yeah
네
If you do it, it will make your dick stand I have an obligation
해주면 좀 더 자지를 빨딱 서게 만들 의무가 있는거야
I will do my best
열심히 할게요
Will you be responsible for cocks?
자지는 책임감이 있으려나?
Something came out from the front
앞쪽에서 뭔가 조금 나왔어
Make the dick more slippery
더 자지를 미끈미끈하게 해
Yeah
네
To give the teacher a more pleasant look I have an obligation
선생님한테 좀 더 기분 좋은 표정을 보여줄 의무가 있는거야
Yeah
네
Now this time
자 이번엔
The teacher will suck the cock
선생님이 입으로 자지를 빨아 줄게
If you suck cocks
자지는 빨아주면
I need to make more cocks, okay?
더 자지를 ㅋ크게 만들어야돼 알겠어?
I know
알겠어요
The teacher does this
선생님이 이렇게 까지 해주잖아
Rice with lots of semen
정액을 많이 쌀
I'm responsible
책임이 있는거야
Yes, I will
네 쌀게요
Can you afford a lot?
많이 쌀수 있겠어?
Can you cook a lot
많이 쌀수 있어요
Pack a lot for the teacher
선생님을 위해서 많이 싸줘
Yeah
네
Teacher ... a little more ...
선생님..조금만더..
Please glans.
귀두쪽을..해주세요
Glans?
귀두?
(Cooper liquid) A lot came out? - Yeah
(쿠퍼액)많이 나왔지? - 네
I feel good - Good?
기분 좋아요 - 좋아?
Ah ... sir ..
아.. 선생님..
So good..
너무 좋아요..
I think it will be cold -Give me a lot
쌀것 같아요.. - 많이 싸줘
It's so warm
엄청 따뜻해
A lot came out
많이 나왔다
I'll wash it clean
선생님이 깨끗하게 빨아 줄게
Yeah
네
What do you think?
어때?
Do you understand the importance of responsibility?
책임감의 중요함이 뭔지 알겠어?
Yeah
네
Production and distribution of subtitles KUKUDAS.COM
자막 제작, 배포 쿠쿠다스닷컴 KUKUDAS.COM
(Good room) When you ordinance,
(양호실) 너 조례할때 고개숙여서
Didn't you see the ass?
엉덩이 보지 않았어?
no
아니
That's it
그거야
It's so pretty
너무 이쁘니까
My chest is not a joke
가슴도 장난 아니야
No no no -Because elasticity is not a joke
아니지 아니지 - 탄력이 장난 아니라니까
Take a look
한번 봐봐
It was a big deal
큰일났어
The teacher is coming behind
선생님 오고 있어 숨어
what?
어라?
My classmates are dingling here. I got a call
우리반 애들이 여기서 땡땡이치고 있다고 연락이 왔는데
Wasn't it here?
여기가 아니었나?
Where are you going?
어디 간거지?
I can't help it
어쩔수 없군
Ah!
아!
I was here too
역시 여기 있었네
Is there more than you? Come out
너 말고 더 있지? 전부 나와
How important is this time
지금이 얼마나 중요한 시기인데
What should I do
땡땡이치면 어떻게 해
I think my stomach hurts.
배가 아픈것 같아서요
Don't be excused
핑계대지 마
Good
좋아
The teacher
선생님이 너희들의 근성을
I'll fix it right away
바로 잡아주겠어
From now on
지금부터
To you, this world I will tell you that it is a competitive society
너희들에게 이 세상은 경쟁사회라는걸 알려주겠어
Competitive society?
경쟁사회요?
okay
그래
Holding hands together and entering the finish line
다 같이 손잡고 결승선에 들어간다니
It's only when you're a student
그런건 학생일때 뿐이야
Okay?
알겠어?
If you know, take it off quickly
알았으면 빨리 벗어
Yeah..
네..
Take off your panties too!
팬티도 벗어야지!
Ah, sorry.
아..죄송합니다..
Among you
너희들중에
To the person who hardened the most cocks
제일 자지를 딱딱하게 만든 사람에게
I will give you the right to have sex with your teacher.
선생님과 섹스할 권리를 주겠어
on? sex? really?
에? 섹스? 정말요?
okay
그래
But there is only one
하지만 한명뿐이야
I just have to see other people.
다른 사람은 보기만 해야돼
character
자
Quickly hardened
빨리 딱딱하게 만들어
Ah yes.. -Ask the teacher to appeal
아..네.. - 선생님한테 어필해 보라고
Quickly hardened
빨리 딱딱하게 만들어
Yeah
네
Don't you want to have sex with your teacher?
선생님하고 섹스하고 싶지 않아?
want to do
하고 싶어요
Then do it quickly
그럼 빨리해
I think something is lacking in stiffness
뭔가 딱딱함이 부족한것 같은데
on? really?
에? 정말요?
Can't help it
어쩔수 없나
The teacher will help a little
선생님이 조금만 도와주겠어
really? Please
정말요? 부탁드립니다
Teacher..
선생님..
So pretty
엄청 이뻐
I have to go
야해요
Teacher's panties
선생님의 팬티
I see well
잘 보여요
Then quickly make it hard - Yeah
그럼 빨리 딱딱하게 만들어 - 네
Wow ~ Awesome
우와~ 끝내주네
Wow ~
우와~ 쩔어
Did you become tight after looking at the panties?
팬티보고 딱딱해졌어?
Yes. It's hard
네. 딱딱해요
Is it really hard?
진짜 딱딱해진거 맞아?
Wow ..
우와.. 엄청나..
Would you like a little more service?
조금만더 서비스 해줄까?
service?
서비스?
Wow ~
와~
Sir ... great ..
선생님.. 대단해요..
I see it
아 다보인다
Would you like to make it a little easier to see?
좀 더 보기 쉽게 해줄까?
Do you see all the teachers?
선생님 보지 다 보이지?
Teacher..
선생님..
Teacher pussy
선생님 보지
Can you see the inside?
안쪽까지 보이지?
Yeah
네
How did it go?
어떻게 됐어?
It's greasy?
번들거리는데?
It's like a tunnel
터널같아요
I'm preparing for the cocks to come in.
자지가 들어올수 있도록 준비를 하는거야
I want to put
넣고 싶어
Who is the hardest?
누가 제일 딱딱하려나?
It's me -It's me.
저에요 저에요 - 저에요
Who is it?
누굴까?
Not enough yet?
아직 부족한데?
Do you not want to put it in your mouth?
선생님 입에 넣고 싶지않아?
I want to put
넣고 싶어요
My mouth is warm
입속이 따뜻해요
Then this time
그럼 이번엔 이쪽
I'm done already? -You're doing it yourself
저 벌써 끝났어요? - 너는 직접하고 있어
Yeah
네
Come on!
자 끝!
I made a little too
저도 좀 만더
Teacher i ...
선생님 저는..
Look at the teacher sucking
선생님이 빨고 있는거 봐줘
Ah ..
아..엄청나요..
Whose cock
누구의 자지가
Are you trying to get into teacher's pussy?
선생님 보지에 들어가려나?
Me Me Me
저요 저요
Make it a little harder
좀 더 딱딱하게 만들어봐
Ah yes..
아..네..
I want to put a teacher
선생님 넣고 싶어요
I am the hardest
제가 제일 딱딱해요
I am the best
제가 최고에요
How to do it ~
어떻게 할까~
No sir I'm more ...
아니 선생님 제가 더..
I want to put it ...
넣고 싶어요..
Do you want to put it in the teacher?
선생님한테 넣고 싶어?
It became so hard
이렇게 딱딱해 졌으니까
Maybe this cock is harder
이쪽 자지가 더 딱딱하려나
It's really hard on me
제꺼 엄청 딱딱해요
Um ... it's pretty hard
음.. 꽤 딱딱하네
right? - no no..
그렇죠? - 아니 아니..
I am the hardest
제가 제일 딱딱해요
Please put -No sir ..
넣어주세요 - 아니 선생님..
What should I do ~
어쩔까~
What about Shimura?
시무라는 어떨까?
I am the hardest
제가 제일 딱딱해요
It's a little hard too
역시 좀 딱딱하긴하네
right?
그렇죠?
No ~
안돼~
I just slipped my foot.
그냥 발이 미끄러진거야
Please ask a teacher -I am the hardest and the biggest
선생님 부탁해요 - 제가 제일 딱딱하고 커요
Not yet ~
아직은 안돼~
Also
역시
Tsukasa-kun's cock was the hardest.
츠카사군의 자지가 제일 딱딱했어
No ... -I'm the best
아니 그런.. - 제가 최고에요
Put it in .. -Would you like it?
넣어주.. - 넣어줄까?
Yeah..
네..
Then take a good look
그럼 잘봐
Going in
들어가는거
Awesome
끝내준다
Good
좋아
Look at what's in now
지금 들어가있는거 잘봐
Is not it?
분하지?
I couldn't put it in my teacher's pussy
선생님 보지에 넣지 못해서
Disassemble
분해요
Don't forget that anger
그 분함을 잊어버리면 안돼
I feel so good that it ’s dangerous.
기분이 너무 좋아서 위험해요
If you keep moving your waist, it will be like this ..
계속 허리 움직이시면 이대로 쌀것같아요..
what?
뭐라고?
What makes you feel so good?
기분이 너무 좋아서 뭐?
It looks cheap ..
싸..쌀것 같아요..
You're only cheap with this?
겨우 이런걸로 싼다고?
I think I'll go ...
갈것 같아요..
Already going? -I'm sorry, it's so good ...
벌써 간다고? - 죄송해요 너무 좋아서요..
It's a competitive society
경쟁사회라고
nevertheless
그렇지만
A ~ So I can't survive
에이~ 그래서는 못 살아남아
Please wait sir ..
기다려주세요 선생님..
I can't help it
어쩔수 없네
I'll see you then
그럼 봐줄테니까
Show me the way to the teacher
선생님한테 가는 모습을 보여줘
Now the teacher will take a look
자 선생님이 봐줄테니까
Pack a lot
많이 싸봐
Yeah
네
That's dangerous ...
그거 위험해요..
Huh?
응?
(Cheap)
(싸도)좋아
Ah, good..
아 좋아..
Ah .. cheap ..
아..싸요..
(Cheap)
(싸도)좋아
It came out hard
거세게 나왔네
Yeah..
네..
Did you get this?
이걸로 알게 됐지?
Yeah
네
The world is a competitive society
세상은 경쟁사회야
If you know, you shouldn't be in the future
알았으면 앞으로 땡땡이치면 안돼
Yeah
네
Production and distribution of subtitles KUKUDAS.COM
자막 제작, 배포 쿠쿠다스닷컴 KUKUDAS.COM
Was this a little bad
이건 좀 심했나
still
그래도
this
이게
Mr. Ito's ...
이토 선생님의..
It's the smell of Mr. Ito ...
이토 선생님의 냄새다..
Oh I forgot
아 까먹었네
It shouldn't be like this, but it's a big deal.
이러면 안돼는데 큰일이네
It hasn't been fixed in the past.
예전부터 고쳐지질 않네
what?
어라?
Where did you put it?
어디다 뒀었지?
I was here
여기 있었는데
what?
어라?
Who is it?
누구야?
Atari County
아타라이군
What are you doing?
뭐 하는거야?
No ..
아니 그게..
Sorry..
죄송합니다..
It's a surprise
깜짝이야
Really
정말
I can't even practice swimming
수영부 연습에도 안나오고
You shouldn't be doing this
이러고 있으면 안되지
Are these my stockings?
이거 내 스타킹이지?
Ah ... sorry ..
아.. 죄송합니다..
Unintentionally ...
무심코..
I don't have any records recently.
최근에 기록이 안나온다고
If I miss practice, my body gets harder
연습을 빠지면 오히려 더 몸이 굳어
Ah ... is it?
아.. 그런가요?
What to do
어떻게 해야할까
How to record well
어떻게해야 기록이 잘나올까
What do we do?
어떡하지?
how should..
어떻게해야..
What should I do ~
어떻게 해야 할까~
How can I get it to practice?
연습을 하게 하려면 어떻게 해야하지?
How to practice Atari's
아타라이군의 연습을 어떻게 해야될까
Also
역시
For newcomers
신입인 선생님한테는
Was it difficult ~?
어려운 일이었나~?
Wow..
와..
How to practice
어떻게해야 연습을 해주려나
I don't know ~
모르겠네~
Atari? - Ah yes..
아타라이군? - 아..네..
Do you like teacher ass?
선생님 엉덩이 좋아해?
No ... that's ...
아니..그게..
Yeah! I really like it
네! 엄청 좋아합니다
Then again
그럼 역시
When a man likes something, does he become motivated?
남자는 좋아하는게 생기면 의욕이 생기지?
I think it will happen
네 생길거라고 생각합니다
then
그럼
Teacher
선생님이
What Atarai-kun likes
아타라이군이 좋아하는걸로
I'll make you motivated
의욕이 생기게 해줄게
really?
정말요?
Then lie down here
그럼 여기 누워봐
Yeah
네
Teacher's ass ...
선생님 엉덩이가..
What do you think?
어때?
It's the best
최고에요
The hips are close ...
엉덩이가.. 가까워..
I touched my face
얼굴에 닿았어
How's your ass?
선생님 엉덩이 어때?
Awesome
끝내줘요
Do you want to see more?
좀 더 보고싶어?
I miss you
보고 싶어요
Isn't it painful?
괴롭지 않아?
It's okay
괜찮아요 최고에요
Teacher what do you want to do
선생님 엉덩이 어떻게 하고 싶어?
I want to touch
만지고 싶어요
then
그럼
Will you practice well?
연습 잘 나올거야?
Yeah
네
I will go out every day
매일 나갈게요
I will practice on Sunday
일요일에도 연습할게요
Would you like to touch it? Teacher ass
만져 볼래? 선생님 엉덩이
It's okay?
괜찮아요?
That's amazing
엄청나네
A firm butt
탱탱한 엉덩이
You can touch it
만져도 돼
Ah teacher ...
아 선생님..
Butt feels awesome
엉덩이 촉감이 끝내줘요
You have to touch
만지는게 야해
is that so?
그런가요?
The swimsuit is very chewy
수영복이 엄청 씹혔어요
Would you like to touch it with more variety?
더 다양한 자세로 만져볼래?
It's okay?
괜찮아요?
Oh ~ kill
오~ 죽인다
I see well
잘 보이네
Atari County
아타라이군
No...
안돼...
Where the teacher feels ...
선생님이 느끼는곳을..
Yes?
그래요?
Then you should touch more
그럼 많이 더 만져야지
I feel good
기분 좋아져버려
No...
안돼...
No..
안돼..
Go away, sir ...
선생님 가버려..
No .. go ..
안돼..가버려..
Ah ... sorry
아.. 죄송해요
I'm so excited ...
너무 흥분되서..
I need to touch the way
만지는 방식이 야하다니까
Do you think it will be okay if you don't like practice?
연습 나오지 싫어하는거 괜찮아 질것 같아?
Yeah
네
Let's go practice something! I feel like
뭔가 연습 나가자! 라는 기분이 들어요
Good
잘됐네
Teacher butt more
선생님 엉덩이 좀 더
Touch it - Yeah
만져봐 - 네
You really like hips.
정말 엉덩이를 좋아하는구나
Teacher
선생님
Can I touch the other side? - Good
반대쪽도 만져도 될까요? - 좋아
Wow ~
와~
Raunchy ass
야한 엉덩이
Did you want to touch the other side?
반대쪽도 만지고 싶었어?
That's ... because your ass is pretty
그게..이렇게 엉덩이가 이쁘니까
I said no
안된다니까 거긴
Finish this butt line
이 엉덩이라인 끝내줘요
Teacher..
선생님..
Is this a good place to stay?
기분 좋은곳이 여기에요?
No..
안돼..
Go again ...
또 가버려..
Teacher
선생님
Are you feeling better?
기분 좋아져버린거에요?
I also
나도
I can't stand it
못 참겠어요
Teacher's here
선생님의 여기
Can I rub it on my butt?
엉덩이에 문질러도 될까요?
Will you practice if you do that?
그렇게 해주면 연습 나올거지?
I want to go to practice
연습 가고 싶어져요
I'm touching
닿고있어
Will you practice well? - Yeah
연습 잘 나올거지? - 네
I'm going to practice
연습 나갈게요
Very hard things are being rubbed
엄청 딱딱한게 문질러지고 있어
Wrap your teacher in the ass a lot
선생님 엉덩이에 많이 싸줘
Can I be cheap?
싸도 돼요?
Can I wrap this in your ass? Really?
선생님의 이 엉덩이에 싸도 돼요? 정말?
You can wrap it in the ass
엉덩이에 싸도 돼
Yeah
네
Teacher..
선생님..
Sir ... ah ...
선생님...아..
I think it will be cold
쌀것 같아요..
Cheap ..
싼다..
A lot
많이 나왔네
Are you so excited about your ass?
선생님 엉덩이에 이렇게 흥분한거야?
You can't miss practice from tomorrow.
내일부터 연습 빠지면 안돼
Production and distribution of subtitles KUKUDAS.COM
자막 제작, 배포 쿠쿠다스닷컴 KUKUDAS.COM
Oh, thank you
아 감사합니다
It's okay
괜찮아요
Where to put it?
어디에 둘까요?
I'm sorry, Mr. Samejima. Isn't it heavy?
죄송해요 사메지마 선생님 무겁지 않으세요?
None is heavy
하나도 안 무거워요
Put it here
여기에 두세요
thank you
고맙습니다
I was in trouble because I couldn't listen alone.
혼자서 못들어서 곤란하던 참이었는데
It's not like this
이정도야 뭐 별일 아니니까
thank you
고맙습니다
But Mr. Ito is really studying hard.
그런데 이토 선생님 진짜 공부 열심히 하시네요
You read a book like this after school
방과후에까지 이렇게 책을 읽다니
No I'm still new
아니에요 아직 제가 신입이라
I have to work harder.
좀 더 열심히 해야죠
I really want other teachers to imitate
정말 다른 선생님들도 본받았으면 좋겠어요
No, Mr. Samejima. Even if you compliment like that
아니에요 사메지마 선생님 그렇게 칭찬해주셔도 드릴게 없어요
No, I didn't think so.
아니 그럴생각은 아니었고요
Then what shall we do today
그럼 오늘은 뭘로 할까
What would you like
뭐가 좋을까요
Ah this would be fun
아 이거 재밌겠네
What can I do
어쩌지
Five..
오..
What to do
뭘로 할까
Samejima teacher
사메지마 선생님
Do you care?
신경쓰이세요?
Yeah? Alas..
네? 아아..
I have an older brother
저 오빠가 있는데요
Like Mr. Samejima
사메지마 선생님 처럼
I always stole my panties
항상 제 팬티를 훔쳐봤어요
No ... that's ...
아니.. 그게..
Sorry
죄송합니다
Samejima teacher
사메지마 선생님
It looks a bit like my brother.
저희 오빠랑 조금 닮았네요
Something's thrilling
뭔가 두근거리네요
Mr. Samejima ...
사메지마 선생님..
I'm watching there! No masturbation!
거기서 보고있어! 자위행위 금지!
Mr. Samejima ...
사메지마 선생님..
Mr. Ito ...
이토 선생님..
I have sensitive ears
저 귀가 민감한데
I'll suck like this
이렇게 빨아 줄게요
So good ...
너무 좋아..
I'm going to be holding Ito's chest.
이토 선생님의 가슴을 주무르게 될줄이야
Please be more tender
더 주물러 주세요
It's okay?
괜찮아요?
more
좀 더
Is it okay to do something like this?
이런짓해도 괜찮아요?
It's really exciting
엄청 두근 거려요
I want to touch it myself
직접 만지고 싶은데
Ito teacher's chest
이토 선생님 가슴
If you are a teacher of Samejima
사메지마 선생님이라면
(Even if you touch it)
(만져도)괜찮아요
really?
정말요?
Shy
부끄러워요
Mr. Samejima ...
사메지마 선생님..
I got caught so tight
이렇게 꽉차게 잡혀서
It's good
좋네요
It's okay?
괜찮아요?
Please suck
빨아 주세요
Suck more
더 빨아주세요
So pretty
엄청 이뻐요
Ah ~
아~ 엄청나네
Is this okay?
이쪽도 괜찮을까요?
Touch
만져주세요
My underwear is sexy
속옷이 야하네요
Very good
아주 좋아요
Would it be okay?
괜찮을까요?
there..
거기..
Please suck
빨아 주세요
This way too -Direct?
이쪽도 - 직접?
Are you okay?
괜찮은거에요?
Mr. Ito ...
이토 선생님..
Mr. Ito's ...
이토 선생님의..
Shy
부끄러워요
Your pussy looks like this.
보지가 이렇게 생겼었군요
Can I see you? - Yeah
보지 봐도 될까요? - 네
Are you really okay?
정말 괜찮아요?
It's definitely wet
분명히 젖어있네요
that..
그게..
because I like it so much..
너무 좋아서..
Good good
좋아 좋아
May I see more?
좀 더 봐도 될까요?
Teacher..
선생님..
Why is it so wet?
왜 이렇게 젖은거에요?
Good..
좋아..
because I like it so much..
너무 좋아서..
No..
안돼..
Ah, good..
아 좋아..
That's amazing ...
엄청나네..
The soup is flowing
국물이 엄청 흐르고 있어요
I can't stop
멈출수가 없어요
No..
안돼..
Mr. Ito ...
이토 선생님..
The classroom ...
교실이..
No..
안돼요..
It's okay
괜찮아요
I miss you ass
엉덩이 보고 싶어요
Get down here
이쪽에 엎드려 보세요
Ah ~ Awesome
아~ 끝내주네
Ass shy
엉덩이 부끄러워요
why?
왜요?
Ito teacher You were wearing such a pretty ass.
이토 선생님 이렇게 이쁜 엉덩이를 하고 있었구나
Ah ~ I can see it all
아~ 다 보이네
Samejima teacher more
사메지마 선생님 좀 더
Yeah
네
I think I'll go ...
갈것 같아요..
Mr. Ito ...
이토 선생님..
Are you gone?
가버리신 거에요?
Yeah
네
this time
이번엔
I will make Mr. Samejima happy.
제가 사메지마 선생님을 기분좋게 해드릴게요
It's okay?
괜찮아요?
Samejima teacher - Yeah
사메지마 선생님 - 네
Ah, good
아 좋아
Mr. Samejima's body is cool
사메지마 선생님 몸이 멋져요
Thank you
감사합니다
Oh no. If you touch it like that ...
아 안돼요.. 그렇게  만지시면..
Can I touch it? - Yeah
만져도 될까요? - 네
Do you feel here?
여기 느껴지세요?
Yes there is sensitive
네 거기 민감해요
that
저
I love people who feel it with their nipples
젖꼭지로 느끼는사람 너무 좋아해요
I want to suck
빨고 싶어져요
Do you do that?
그런것도 해주는거에요?
May I see the cock of Mr. Samejima?
사메지마 선생님의 자지 봐도 될까요?
Yeah
네
A little embarrassing
조금 부끄럽지만
Wow ...
와.. 엄청나
Mr. Samejima ...
사메지마 선생님..
It's big
자지 크네요
Shy
부끄러워요
It's really hot
엄청 뜨거워요
Ah, good
아 좋아
Do you feel good?
자지 기분 좋아요?
Mr. Ito ...
이토 선생님..
Can I wash it?
빨아도 될까요?
Are you sucking? - Yeah
빨아주시는 거에요? - 네
I can't stand it
못 참겠어요
I sucked hard cock like this
이렇게 딱딱한 자지를 빨았더니
Samejima teacher
사메지마 선생님
This cock
이 자지
Please put - It's okay?
넣어 주세요 - 괜찮아요?
Yeah
네
Because you said that
그렇게 말씀해 주셧으니까
I can't take it anymore
더 이상 못 참아요
Ah
아 들어간다
Ah Ito ...
아 이토 선생님..
Mr. Samejima ...
사메지마 선생님..
Ah, good..
아 좋아..
Good
좋아
Samejima's cock
사메지마 선생님의 자지
Deep inside
깊숙히 들어와서
Mr. Samejima ...
사메지마 선생님..
Samejima teacher
사메지마 선생님
Please put more
더 박아주세요
go away..
가버려..
Go again ...
또 가버려..
Mr. Ito ...
이토 선생님..
Can I put it?
넣어도 될까요?
Please put
넣어주세요
Mr. Ito ...
이토 선생님..
I really like it
엄청 들어가서 좋아
Samejima teacher
사메지마 선생님
So good
너무 좋아요
I like it too
저도 좋아요
Please put a lot
많이 박아주세요
It's okay?
괜찮아요?
So good
너무 좋아요
Go again ...
또 가버려...
Samejima teacher
사메지마 선생님
Do you like my pussy?
제 보지 기분 좋으세요?
So good
너무 좋아요
Can you get on the top?
위에 올라타 주실래요?
I like it too
저도 그거 좋아해요
then..
그런..
Ah, there you go ...
아..거기..가버려..
Go..
가요..
Oh good
아 좋네
So good
너무 좋아요
I can't do it.
안되겠다 허리 움직이면 너무 좋아서
Can I put it back? - Yeah
뒤로 넣어도 될까요? - 네
Mr. Samejima ... - why?
사메지마 선생님.. - 왜요?
Mr. Ito ...
이토 선생님..
No .. go ..
안돼..가버려..
I'll put it back
다시 넣을게요
Mr. Samejima ...
사메지마 선생님..
So good
너무 좋아요
Please make me feel good
많이 기분 좋게 해주세요
Ah, good
아 좋아
So good ...
너무 좋아..
Mr. Samejima ...
사메지마 선생님..
I think it will be cold
쌀것 같아요
Please pack a lot
많이 싸주세요
A lot of..
많이..
Is it okay to wrap my mouth?
입에 싸도 괜찮을까요?
Please wrap
싸주세요
Oh, no..
아 안돼..
Samejima teacher Did you feel good?
사메지마 선생님 기분 좋으셧어요?
It was really good
엄청 좋았어요
Come into the classroom
교실로 들어와
Have you been patient?
계속 참고 있었어?
Ah ... yes.
아.. 네.. 참았어요
The teacher told you
선생님이 너한테
It's to teach patience.
인내를 가르치기 위해서 그런거야
Yeah
네
It was hard, though?
그래도 힘들었지?
Want to be liberated?
해방되고 싶지?
Lying there - Yeah
거기에 누워 - 네
The teacher will liberate you
선생님이 해방시켜 줄게
Wow ~
와~
You've got an erection when you see your teacher having sex.
선생님이 섹스하는거보고 발기했구나
The teacher will liberate you
선생님이 해방시켜줄게
Good? - Yeah
좋아? - 네
Ah there ...
아 거기..
I love it there
거기 엄청 좋아요
Will it be just your mouth?
입만으로 되겠어?
Put up like that
그렇게 참아놓고
Don't you want to be liberated by teacher pussy?
선생님 보지로 해방되고 싶지 않아?
want to do
하고 싶어요
With teacher's pussy
선생님의 보지로
then
그럼
Because I've been patient for a long time, I'll reward you
오래 참았으니까 상을줄게
I went in
들어갔어
Ah teacher ...
아 선생님..
Did you get into teacher's pussy?
선생님 보지에 들어갔어?
I went in
들어갔어요
I'm in the pussy
보지에 들어가 있어요
You can move from the bottom
밑에서 움직여도 돼
Yeah
네
Teacher pussy
선생님 보지에
Cock You can feel better
참았던 자지 많이 기분 좋아져도돼
Yeah
네
Oh it's really hot
아 엄청 뜨거워요
The teacher's pussy is really hot
선생님 보지 엄청 뜨거워요
Please drive a lot
많이 박아줘
good
좋아요
Good..
좋아..
Please drive me a lot
자지 많이 박아줘
go away..
가버려..
Oh no ... go ..
아 안돼.. 간다..
Ah .. awesome ..
아.. 끝내준다..
I have to feel a lot better
많이 기분 좋아져야돼
come here
이쪽으로 와
By moving directly
직접 움직여서
You can feel a lot better
많이 기분좋아 져도 돼
Ah ... awesome
아아.. 끝내줘요
I went inside the teacher
선생님 안까지 들어갔어
With the teacher (I want to go)
선생님이랑 같이 (가고싶어요)
I'll go
갈게요
I came out a lot because I was patient
참고 있었어서 많이 나왔네
Today ’s patience is
오늘의 배운 인내력은
It would be very helpful to go to society.
사회에 나가면 많이 도움이 될거야
Production and distribution of subtitles KUKUDAS.COM
자막 제작, 배포 쿠쿠다스닷컴 KUKUDAS.COM